Hello Hello Friends, my name is Rahul Jain.
Welcome to our YouTube channel.
Today we are going to talk about Tata AIG
Medical Treatment Plant. Friends, if
you watch this video, you will get
complete information about this plant, so that
you can subscribe for yourself.
If you
subscribe, then
subscribe. If I take it upon myself, then it
comes under the family floater plan. So, here we will
talk about all the methods. If you want to subscribe under this, then
subscribe here. You will get seven-member
coverage only. Next, we will talk about subscribe. Do subscribe.
Otherwise, subscribe here.
Above that, I mean, the
square
appointed
subscribe separately. If you look here,
if you
subscribe, then do
subscribe.
If you
subscribe and they presented a
misguided mixture of this company, then
what can the company do by cancelling the
policy tomorrow? They can cancel the policy
and will not even fulfill the time given by you. So, it
means that
whoever you
subscribe to, you cannot subscribe to the policy of the new company. This means
that war is the
meaning of the policy.
Screen
appointment, so we are given 30 days
extra time for a problem so that we
can do simple work, we are getting time every day,
that is home appointment
subscribe,
definitely subscribe
subscribe
[music]
appointment so
you should subscribe in any company only at the
time of
subjects airplane setting airlines means
that if you want to increase your time, today
you have earned 5 lakhs and if you think that
you want to earn 10 lakhs or 15 lakhs then that is
possible only at that time which is for company meeting
subscribe
subscribe if you have not yet subscribed to our channel then
you should
subscribe here subscribe
hearing approval of ideal and will be intimated to you at least
three months in
advance
subscribe
withdrawal subscribe
if you
subscribe
appoint you will get information about the liquid done in this way
then you should
subscribe
now
subscribe to skin if
not subscribe so
when we want to take the benefit of the policy then
two-four means that 24 hour hospitalization is a
matter, only then we will get the
benefit of the claim money here
Secondly, you can talk to them here and suppose
if I had taken a policy and it gets
cancelled and when it comes to the tractor, the
company has to
subscribe
to the channel, if
jobs are not available or the
patient is in such a condition that you have to take him from home
to the hospital, then in that
condition the company has a pistol
from the doctor, basically you can
subscribe to any channel, subscribe to the channel,
subscribe to the channel, now
let's set up the school here
and for the family,
here for
placing your family member from this particular place, the
maximum expense starts up to twenty rupees,
which you can take later, so you will have to bear the expenses,
subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, so if you subscribe
and
subscribe
like and
subscribe,
if you
subscribe, then there are
subscriptions,
like sir, if we
consulted a doctor, there may be some consultancy or
medicines, then there may be expenses for that,
if there are reports, then you can keep those as well,
I can subscribe to small subscriptions in advance, that is,
school, so that
you can avail your benefits here.  If you are
subscribed
then here we are going to
give the benefit of crop health checkup of computer labs, we will
talk about it and
benefits like nine treatments, that means
if you subscribe to this channel for the benefit of MS Word, there is
no need to subscribe to the channel, that means if we
talk about getting the full money of [music] school, then if I had
taken a policy of 10 lakhs next year, then next
year my bank will give me 15 lakhs, if I have
not made any claim, if I
subscribe to the Niyukti, there is
no need to subscribe to the channel, you are
seeing that
subscribe, subscribe,
more than half means 40 in the
whole of India,
subscribe,
now what happens is that we will talk about the
benefits from this, okay now we will talk about
subscription, that means
subscribe to my channel,
subscribe,
in every company under Niyukti Quality,
here you will get one, 2 years'
wait for the meeting of the forum and these are some
limited diseases, subscribe from all the companies, if there is a
problem, then
subscribe,
if you
subscribe to
Niyukti, whatever happens, then
subscribe to it.
Subscribe
that if suppose today I took a policy and
I already had some disease, okay, that
disease, here I have to
subscribe to some company for two years, so
if any person
soon
then I will tell you that you should subscribe to this,
medical and health
benefits, but here there are some
things and no one ever completes them, which is
very important for us to know, like we will talk about
them, any company and subscribe,
subscribe to the channel,
like and
so here I have said that now here we will talk about
defects and roti in a jar,
suppose there is a person who is not normal, the
company does not cover his problem here,
okay, you should keep this
in mind,
subscribe if you
subscribe
and
subscribe to the channel, if
you suffer such an injury, like you want to
take the benefit, then the company is
not covering you even if you
try to attempt suicide,
okay, I mean if you do all those things, then the
companies are not commenting on
this attempting suicide
Printer's
war breaks and if you do
not subscribe then
here
I have told you that you
can also subscribe to the war benefits, like if you get
such appointment then
share it in the subscribe and stay with us so that you do not get
such appointment,
thank you,
subscribe and press the bell icon.